var data = [{
	"question":"First artificial satellite sent in space was",
	"a":"Sputnik 1",
	"b":"Sputnik 2",
	"c":"Explorer 1",
	"d":"Explorer 2",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"A dog sent in first flight to space was named",
	"a":"Laika",
	"b":"Jupiter",
	"c":"Lucky",
	"d":"Luna",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Space-age spinoffs includes",
	"a":"smoke detectors",
	"b":"invisible braces",
	"c":"medical laser",
	"d":"all of them",
	"ans":"d"
},{
	"question":"A GPS is composed of solar powered satellites which are in number",
	"a":"72",
	"b":"27",
	"c":"34",
	"d":"47",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"First man who set foot in space was",
	"a":"Yuri Gagarian",
	"b":"Jules Verne",
	"c":"Neil Armstrong",
	"d":"Aldrin",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Space probe which discovered crates on moon was",
	"a":"Voyager",
	"b":"Pioneer",
	"c":"Clementine",
	"d":"Venera",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"In 1966 first space probe which landed on moon was",
	"a":"Luna 1",
	"b":"Luna 9",
	"c":"Sputnik 1",
	"d":"Terra 1",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"A long-term platform which provides medium for research in space is called",
	"a":"spacecraft",
	"b":"spacestation",
	"c":"spaceshuttle",
	"d":"spacesatellite",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Flight of first space craft lasted for",
	"a":"180 mins",
	"b":"108 mins",
	"c":"80 mins",
	"d":"8 mins",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Upward pushing of aircraft by engine is called its",
	"a":"velocity",
	"b":"centrifugal force",
	"c":"gravity",
	"d":"thrust",
	"ans":"d"
}]